## STEVEN HARJAPRAMANA

WEB DEVELOPER, PROGRAMMER

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

81 A'Beckett Street Melbourne, 3000

#### PHONE

0413695516

#### **EMAIL**

stevenharja@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, React, CSS

BigCommerce, Shopify, Woocommerce, Wordpress

XERO, MYOB, Sage, Pronto, SquareUp, Ordermentum, NetSuite

Multitasking, Client Management, Project Management, Communication

#### **PROFILE**

Web Developer and Programmer with many experience surrounding creating apps, using API of many different eCommerce platforms such as BigCommerce, Shopify and Woocommerce.

Capable in managing tasks, prioritizing them to what is necessary for the business, and adaptable to many different platforms or frameworks.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Web Developer, Kobe Creations

Melbourne

Aug 2021 — Present

- Develop custom front-end or back-end code for many different types
  of businesses to fit within their customized needs across many different
  e-commerce platforms (Ex: Shopify, BigCommerce and Woocommerce)
- Maintain customer relationships by being timely on support emails, calls and other tickets, and answering them to the best of my abilities.
- Develop together as a team to provide value to the project and the business.

## Programmer, MyIntegrator

Melbourne

Dec 2021 — Present

- Create and connect businesses enterprise software or platform to their e-commerce website through a middleman service that is custom developed for each business based on their requirements.
- Software integrated or developed with: BigCommerce, Shopify,
   Woocommerce, Wordpress, Sage ERP, Pronto ERP, SquareUp, MYOB AR,
   MYOB Advanced, MYOB EXO, Ordermentum, NetSuite, XERO
- Develop new integration for many different enterprise software using their
   API / direct database access focused on e-commerce and businesses.

## Web Developer & Administrator, Bernies Music Land

Melbourne

Nov 2020 — Sep 2021

- Updating the website content, which includes deleting obsolete pages, adding new pages, events or products as instructed.
- Troubleshoot technical issues for staffs and assisting them with relevant tasks or issues.
- Assisting with maintaining online presence of the business, which involves publishing events to the website and facebook, and Mailchimp

## EDUCATION

## Master of Computer Science, RMIT University

Melbourne

2020 — 2021

- · Graduated with Distinction
- · Grade: 3.5 GPA

## Melbourne

# Bachelor of Information Technology, Monash University

2018 — 2020

· Grade: 3.0 GPA

· Major: Business Information Systems